atomz.com 2000-12-06

# Privacy Statement

**Atomz.com Privacy Statement**  
Avivo Corporation, the creator of Atomz.com, is committed to honoring the privacy of Atomz.com members and visitors. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Our site's registration form requires members to give us contact information (like their name and email address). Other forms on our site require members to provide financial information (like their account or credit card numbers) when upgrading to one of our paid services. We use member contact information from the registration form to send the member information about our services and promotional material from partners. We use financial information to bill the member for products and services. WE DO NOT SELL, TRADE, EXCHANGE OR OTHERWISE MAKE AVAILABLE ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANY OTHER COMPANY OR ORGANIZATION. 

The member contact information is also used to contact the member periodically about their account, and in these mailings we may include offers from our partners. Other than what is mentioned above, we will not send you unsolicited information, commercial offers, and advertisements. 

This site contains links to other sites. Atomz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

As part of the Atomz.com Search service we will index a site or sites that you provide us the URL or URLs for. We clearly identify the Atomz.com robot when we index these sites and respect the Robots Exclusion Protocol and the Robots META tags. If the owners of the site do not want us to index their site, we will respect their ownership of the site and desist from indexing their web site. 

**Cookies**  
Our site does not use cookies. Authentication information is encrypted and passed from page to page as you use the site. If you do not use the site for a half hour this authentication information expires. 

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. In the course of delivering an ad to you DoubleClick collects certain non-personally identifiable information about you using cookies. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures of DoubleClick, please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy.html).While we do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies may be received with banner ads by Doubleclick, and we do not have access to this information. In addition, the advertising company does not have access to the Atomz.com member's personally identifiable information. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our site uses firewall and encryption technology to protect your information, and our servers are located in a guarded co-location facility under 24-hour surveillance. 

**Canceling Your Membership**  
By becoming a member of Atomz.com, you agree that we may contact you regarding your account as described above. To not receive these communications, you may cancel your membership at the following URL: http://www.atomz.com/members/accounts. 

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives members the ability to change and modify information previously provided. Please visit http://www.atomz.com/members/accounts/

**Contacting Atomz.com about Privacy**  
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Atomz.com site coordinator, at [privacy@atomz.com](mailto:privacy@atomz.com). You may also use this address to notify us that you do not wish to receive future mailings from Atomz.com.
